Okay, the drink we're about to make is called Emerald Isle Cocktail.
And this is going to be served as a martini, up, with no ice.
So if you get your martini glass ready with some water and ice in it, let that sit for about thirty seconds, and it'll be nice and chilled when you're ready to serve.
All right, measure out two ounces of gin.
There we go.
And follow that up with a half a shot of green creme de menthe.
And last we will add three dashes of bitters.
There's one, two, and three.
Now, let's mix this up real well.
Get it nice and cold.
Since we're serving it up, want to make sure you shake it very well before you pour.
And that'll do it.
And that'll do it. Go ahead and grab your glass. And strainer. And pour it in. Got a nice, pretty green color.
Go ahead and grab your glass.
And strainer.
And pour it in.
Got a nice, pretty green color.
There we go.
That'll do it.
Emerald Isle Cocktail.
Bottoms up.